A Guide to the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission Yucca Mountain Research Collection TD898.12.N3 U85
University of Nevada, Reno. DeLaMare Science & Engineering Library
- Oversby, V.M. "Spent fuel as a waste form-data needs to allow long term performance assessment under repository disposal conditions." From Scientific Basis for Nuclear Waste Management X. (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Orthen, R.F. Jr. "Health, safety, and environmental impacts during controlled long-term storage of spent nuclear fuel and high-level radioactive waste in the United States." Tetra Tech NUS, Inc. (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory. "Technical apendix, our nation's travel 1995 NPTS early results report." (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Office of Management and Budget. "Definition of poverty for statistical purposes, statistical policy directive no. 14." (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Nuclear Energy Agency, Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development, Working Group on Integrated Performance Assessments of Deep Repositories. "Lessons learnt from ten performance assessment studies." (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Nuclear Waste Project Office, Agency for Nuclear Projects. "Review and critique of the experimental design for the Yucca Mountain ecological effects studies: A report to the U.S. Department of Energy." (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Nevada State Health Division. "Low-level waste site post-closure activities." (Box 56, Folder 6)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC issues certificate to General Atomics for transportation cask for spent nuclear fuel." (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Private Fuel Storage, L.L.C. "Environmental report, private fuel storage facility, docket no. 72-22: Skull Valley Indian Reservation Tooele County, Utah." Introduction - appendix 2D. (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Private Fuel Storage, L.L.C. "Environmental report, private fuel storage facility, docket no. 72-22: Skull Valley Indian Reservation Tooele County, Utah." Ch. 3-7. (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Private Fuel Storage, L.L.C. "Environmental report, private fuel storage facility, docket no. 72-22: Skull Valley Indian Reservation Tooele County, Utah." Ch. 8-9. (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Private Fuel Storage, L.L.C. "Environmental report, private fuel storage facility, docket no. 72-22: Skull Valley Indian Reservation Tooele County, Utah." Ch. 2 rev. 1. (Box 56, Folder 11)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Interim NRR procedure for environmental reviews." (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Nevada Power Company. "Nevada Power Company 1997 resource plan executive summary." Vol. 1. (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project. "Maps of biological resources along transportation corridors and intermodal transfer stations [technical data tracking system list]. (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Nevada Legistative Counsel Bureau. "Local financial reporting statewide summary report: Counties cities school districts revenues and expenditures FY 1993-94 (actual) - FY 1996-97 (budget)." (Box 56, Folder 15)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Nevada Field Office. "Underground redionuclide migration at the Nevada Test Site." DOE/NV-346 UC-703. (Box 56, Folder 16)
- U.S. Department of Transportation, National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. "Traffic safety facts 1997." (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Neuhauser, K.S. and Kanipe, F.L. "RADTRAN 4: Volume 3 user guide." Sandia National Laboratories. SAND89-2370 TTC-0943 UC-722 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Nevada Division of Water Planning. "Nevada hydrographic regions/basins." (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Nevada Division of Water Planning. "Nevada water facts, surface and ground-water quality." (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Nevada Division of Water Planning. "Nevada water facts: Northwest region - groundwater basin information." (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Nevada Department of Transportation. "The annual traffic report." (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Nevada Department of Conservation and Natural Resources. "State of Nevada Bureau of Air Quality 1988-1997 trends report." (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Nevada Department of Conservation and Natural Resources. "1997 ground water pumpage inventory." (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Nevada Department of Conservation and Natural Resources. "Class II air quality operating permit." No. AP9611-0573. (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Nevada Department of Conservation and Natural Resources. "Water for Nevada 3: Nevada's water resources." (Box 57, Folder 10)
- National Council on Radiation Protection and Measurements. "Screening models for releases of radionuclides to atmosphere, surface water, and ground." NCRP Report no. 123 I. (Box 58, Folder 1)
- National Council on Radiation Protection and Measurements. "Screening models for releases of radionuclides to atmosphere, surface water, and ground - work sheets." NCRP Report no. 123 II. (Box 58, Folder 2)
- National Council on Radiation Protection and Measurements. "Ionizing radiation exposure of the population of the United States." NCRP report no. 93. (Box 58, Folder 3)
- National Council on Radiation Protection and Measurements. "Risk estimates for radiation protection." NCRP report no. 115. (Box 58, Folder 4)
- National Council on Radiation Protection and Measurements. "Limitation of exposure to ionizing radiation." NCRP report no. 116 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- National Research Council. "Nuclear wastes: Technologies for separations and transmutation." (Box 58, Folder 6)
- National Research Council. "Technical bases for Yucca Mountain standards." (Box 58, Folder 7)
- National Research Council. "Ground water at Yucca Mountain: How high can it rise?" (Box 58, Folder 8)
- "Yucca Mountain draft environmental impact statement: Reference information August 1999 & Yucca Mountain supplement to the draft environmental impact statement: Reference information May 2001." (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Stoffle, R.W., Halmo, D.B., Olmsted, J.E. et al. "Native American cultural resource studies at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." (Box 59, Folder 2)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "The distribution and relative abundance of desert tortoises at Yucca Mountain." B00000000-01717-5705-00033. (Box 59, Folder 3)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Engineering design climatology and regional meteorological conditions report." B00000000-01717-5707-00066 REV 00. (Box 59, Folder 4)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems, Inc. "Nevada potential repository preliminary transportation strategy: Study 2." B00000000-01717-4600-00050. Vol. 1. (Box 59, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of Health and Human Services. "Monthly vital statistics report." (Box 59, Folder 6)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 1: Introduction." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment." B00000000-01717-4301-00001, revision 01. (Box 60, Folder 1)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 2: Unsaturated zone hydrology model." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment." B00000000-01717-4301-00002, revision 01. (Box 60, Folder 2)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 3: Thermal hydrology." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment. B00000000-01717-4301-00003, revision 01. (Box 60, Folder 3)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 4: Unsaturated zone hydrology model." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment." B00000000-01717-4301-00004, revision 01. (Box 60, Folder 4)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 5: Waste package degradation modeling abstraction." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment. B00000000-01717-4301-00005, revision 01. (Box 60, Folder 5)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 6: Waste form degradation, radionuclide mobilization and transport through the engineered barrier system." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment. B00000000-01717-4301-00006, revision 01. (Box 60, Folder 6)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 7: Unsaturated zone radionuclide transport." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment. B00000000-01717-4301-00007, revision 01. (Box 60, Folder 7)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 8: Saturated zone flow transport." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment. B00000000-01717-4301-00008, revision 01. (Box 60, Folder 8)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 9: Biosphere." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment. B00000000-01717-4301-00009, revision 01. (Box 61, Folder 1)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 10: Disruptive events." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment. B00000000-01717-4301-00010, revision 01. (Box 61, Folder 2)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Chapter 11: Summary and conclusion." From Total System performance Assessment-Viability Assessment. B00000000-01717-4301-00011, revision 01. (Box 61, Folder 3)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "1998 waste acceptance, storage, and transportation life cycle cost report." A10000000-01717-5708-00003, revision 00. (Box 61, Folder 4)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Efficacy of relocating desert tortoises for the Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project." B00000000-01717-5705-00032, revision 00. (Box 61, Folder 5)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Off-site utilities preliminary assessment" B00000000-01717-5705-00091, revision 00. (Box 61, Folder 6)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Classification and map of vegetation at Yucca and Little Skull Mountains." B00000000-01717-5705-00083, revision 00B. (Box 61, Folder 7)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Radioactivity in FY 1997 groundwater samples from wells and springs near Yucca Mountain." Revision 00. (Box 61, Folder 8)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Nevada transportation engineering file." (Box 62, Folder 1)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental impact statement cost summary report." B00000000-01717-5700-0029, revision 01. (Box 62, Folder 2)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file for land use." B00000000-01717-5700-0029 REV 00. (Box 62, Folder 3)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file: Meteorology and air quality." B00000000-01717-5705-00126 REV 00. (Box 62, Folder 4)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Geology/hydrology environmental baseline file." B00000000-01717-5700-00127 REV 01, DCN 1. (Box 62, Folder 5)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file for water resources." B00000000-01717-5705-00118 REV 01. (Box 62, Folder 6)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file for biological resources." B00000000-01717-5700-00009 REV 00. (Box 62, Folder 7)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file for soils." B00000000-01717-5700-00007 REV 00. (Box 62, Folder 8)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file: Archaeological resources." B00000000-01717-5705-00122 REV 00. (Box 62, Folder 9)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project environmental baseline file for socioeconomics." B00000000-01717-5705-00125 REV 01. (Box 62, Folder 10)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file for human health." B00000000-01717-5705-00114 REV 01. (Box 62, Folder 11)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file: Aesthetics." B00000000-01717-5705-00082 REV 00. (Box 62, Folder 12)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file for environmental justice." B00000000-01717-5705-00123 REV 01. (Box 62, Folder 13)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Impact of radioactive waste heat on soil temperatures." BA000000-01717-5700-00030 REV 0. (Box 62, Folder 14)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Final report: Plant and soil related processes along a natural thermal gradient at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." B0000000-01717-5705-00109 REV 00. (Box 62, Folder 15)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Safety and health plan." B0000000-01717-4600-00016 REV 03. (Box 62, Folder 16)
- TRW Environmental Safety Systems Inc. "Environmental baseline file for national transportation, with data files." B0000000-01717-5705-00116 REV 01. (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Department of Conservation and Natural Resources, Division of Water Resources. "In the matter of application 52338 filed to appropriate the waters from an underground source within the Forty Mile Canyon-Jackass Flats Groundwater Basin, Nye County, Nevada." Ruling #3870. (Box 62, Folder 18)
- U.S. Supreme Court. "United States v. Dann, 1985, 470 U.S. 39 (1985)." (Box 62, Folder 19)
- U.S. Department of the Air Force. "Renewal of the Nellis Air Force range land withdrawal: Department of the Air Force legislative environmental impact statement." Vol. 1. (Box 63, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of the Air Force. "Renewal of the Nellis Air Force range land withdrawal: Department of the Air Force legislative environmental impact statement." Vol. 2. (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 1. Introduction-ch.3. (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 1. Ch. 4-5. (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 1. Ch. 6-7. (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 1. Ch. 8-9. (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 2 appendices. Appendix A-D. (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 2 appendices. Appendix E: pp. AARi-Figure DFS-20. (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 2 appendices. Appendix E: pp. SBK-I to ASM-A6-13. (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 2 appendices. Appendix E: pp. RYA-I to SDO-A2-15. (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 3 appendices. Appendix F. (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Civilian Radioactive Waste Management System. "Probabilistic seismic hazard analyses for fault displacement and vibratory ground motion at Yucca Mountain, Nevada. Final Report." Volume 3 appendices. Appendix G-L. (Box 64, Folder 10)
- U.S. Geological Survey, U.S. Department of the Interior. "Water fact sheet: What is ground water?" (Box 65, Folder 1)
- U.S. Navy. "Record of decision for a dry storage container system for the management of naval spent nuclear fuel," (Box 65, Folder 2)
- U.S. Navy. "Second record of decision for a dry storage container system for the management of naval spent nuclear fuel." (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Utah State University. "Nevada GAP analysis project, geographic information systems coverage." (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Waddell, R.K. "Two-dimensional, steady-state model of ground-water flow, Nevada Test Site and vicinity, Nevada-California." U.S. Geological Survey water resources investigations 82-4085. (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Walker, G.E. and Eakin, T.E. "Ground-water resources - reconnaissance series report 14: Geology and ground water of Amargosa Desert, Nevada-California." U.S. Department of the Interior, U.S. Geological Survey. (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Weiss, S.I., Noble, D.C. and Larson, L.T. "Hydrothermal origin and significance of pyrite in ash-flow tuffs at Yucca Mountain, Nevada." From Economic Geology. (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Wernicke, B., Davis, J.L, Bennett, R.A., et al. "Anomalous strain accumulation in the Yucca Mountain area, Nevada." From Science. (Box 65, Folder 8)
- United States District Court, District of Nevada. "[Western Shoshone National Council et al. v. United States of America et al.: Plaintiffs' opposition to defendants' motion to dismiss.]" CV-S-97-327-HDM (RLH). (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Sandia National Laboratories. "Total-system performance assessment for Yucca Mountain - SNL second iteration (TSPA-1993)." Vol. 1. (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Sandia National Laboratories. "Total-system performance assessment for Yucca Mountain - SNL second iteration (TSPA-1993)." Vol. 2. (Box 65, Folder 11)
- U.S. Department of the Interior. "Hydrogeological and hydrochemical framework, South-Central Great Basin, Nevada-California, with special reference to the Nevada Test Site." Geological professional paper 712-C. (Box 66, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of the Interior. "Maps for hydrogeological and hydrochemical framework, South-Central Great Basin, Nevada-California, with special reference to the Nevada Test Site." Geological professional paper 712-C. (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Yuan, Y.C., Chen, S.Y., Biwer, B.M. et al. RISKIND - A computer program for calculating radiological consequences and health risks from transportation of spent nuclear fuel." ANL/EAD-1. Environmental Assessment Division, Argonne National Laboratory. (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Zocher, M. "[Telephone conversation with G. Brennon, Pacific Northern Rail Contractors Corp. re: quantities of steel rail and concrete rail ties]." Jason Technologies. (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Zabranski, D. "Stainless steel clad commercial SNF - as of May 1998. Email communication with J. Rivers." U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Davis, N.R. and Wells, M.N. "high-level waste system plan revision 8 (U)." HLW-OVP-97-0068. High Level Waste Management Division, Westinghouse Savannah River Company. (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Dirkmaat, P.J. "Response to repository environmental impact statement (EIS) draft appendix A review action items; additional comments (OPE-SFP-98-140)." U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Dirkmaat, P.J. "Response to U.S. Department of Energy (DOE) appendix A MEPAS input parameters review, and miscellaneous data - Yucca Mountain Repository environmental impact statement (EIS)" (OPE-SFP-98-171. (Box 66, Folder 8)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "An evaluation of commercial repository capacity for the disposal of defense high-level waste." (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory. "Characteristics of potential repository waters." DOE/RW-0184-R1. Vol. 1. (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory. "Characteristics of potential repository waters." DOE/RW-0184-R1. Vol. 2. (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory. "Characteristics of potential repository waters." DOE/RW-0184-R1. Vol. 3. (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory. "Characteristics of potential repository waters." DOE/RW-0184-R1. Vol. 4. (Box 67, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Amendment to the record of decision for the Department of Energy (DOE) programmatic spent nuclear fuel management and Idaho National Engineering Laboratory (INEL) environmental restoration and waste management programs environmental impact statements (EIS)." (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Energy Information Administration, Office of Coal, Nuclear, Electric and Alternate Fuels. "Nuclear power generation and fuel cycle report 1997." DOE/EIA-0436(97). (Box 67, Folder 6)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Memorandum: Proposed mix of DOE-owned high level waste and spent nuclear fuel." (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Filmore, D.L. "Parameter selection for Department of Energy spent nuclear fuel to be used in the Yucca Mountain viability assessment." Idaho National Engineering Laboratory and Lockheed Martin. INEEL/EXT-98-00666. (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Fowler, J.R., Edwards, R.E., Marra, S.L. et al. "Chemical composition projections for the DWPF product (U)." WSRC-IM-91-116-1 Revision 1. (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Goff, K.M. "[Revision to original INEEL response to Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Office data call for high-level waste (ref. Palmer and Benedict to Wichmann, July 2, 1997. Memorandum to M.B. Heiser (Lockheed Martin Idaho Technologies Company)]." Argonne National Laboratory-West. (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Goff, K.M. "[ANL-West comments from review of apendix A - Yucca Mountain Repository environmental impact statement. Memorandum to M.G. Heiser (Lockheed Martin Idaho Technologies Corporation)]." Argonne National Laboratory-West. (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Heiser, M.B. "[INEL HLW vit breakdown. Facsimile to J. Rivers, Jason Associates, Inc.]." Lockheed Martin Idaho Technologies Corporation. (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Lockheed Martin Idaho Technologies Corporation. "DOE national spent nuclear fuel database." Version 3.2. (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Knecht, D.A., Valentine, J.H., Luptak, A.J. et al. "Options for determining equivalent MTHM for DOE high-level waste." Idaho National Engineering and Environmental Laboratory, Lockheed Martin. (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Idaho National Engineering & Environmental Laboratory. "Accelerating cleanup: Paths to closure Idaho Operations Office (PLN-177)." (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Lytle, J.E. "[Disposal of DOE-owned high level waste and spent nuclear fuel. Memorandum to D.A. Dreyfus, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management]." Department of Energy. (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Marra, S.L., Harbour, J.R. and Plodinec, M.J. "DWPF Canister procurement, control, drop-test, and closure (U)." Westinghouse Savannah River Company. WSRC-IM-91-116-8, Revision 1. (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Murphy, B.D. "[EIS Jason requests. Memorandum to K.A. Williams]." Oak Ridge National Laboratory. (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Palmer, W.B. "[Clarification to Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Office data call for high level waste-WBP-13-97. Letter to T.L. Wichmann, DOE]." Idaho National Engineering Laboratory. (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Pearson, W.D. "SRS data request followup. Email communication to J. Rivers, Jason Associates Corporation]." U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Pearson, R. "[Status of Mox in RFP. Memorandum to J. Rivers, Jason Associates Corporation]." U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Picha, K.G. Jr. "[Response to repository environmental impact statement data call for high-level waste. Memorandum to W. Dixon, Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Office]." Office of Waste Management, U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Picha, K.G. Jr. "[Clarification of high-level waste and special performance assessment required data for repository environmental impact statement. Memorandum to K. Skipper, Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Office]." Office of Waste Management, U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Picha, K.G. Jr. "[Special performance assessment required waste supplement for the Yucca Mountain repository environmental impact statement. Memorandum to W. Dixon, Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Office]." Office of Waste Management, U.S. Department of Energy. (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Picha, K.G. Jr. "[Follow up response to repository EIS data call for high-level waste. Memorandum to W. Dixon]." U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Waste Management. (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Oak Ridge National Laboratory. "Characteristics of spent fuel from plutonium disposition reactors vol. 2: A general electric boiling water-reactor design." ORNL/TM-13170/V2. (Box 68, Folder 17)